Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 71, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Reemployment Provisions of Universal Military Training and Service Act and Retired Service-Man's Family Protection Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Armed Services
    Notes: July 25, 1968
  - Item 2: Dual Compensation Act Report, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Post Office and Civil Service
    Notes: February 23, 1966
  - Item 3: Amending and Clarifying the Reemployment Rights of Persons Who Reform Military Service, 1968; Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)
    Notes: July 26, 1968
  - Item 4: Dual Compensation Act Report, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Item 5: An Examination of the Transferability of Certain Military Skills and Experience to Civilian Occupations, 1967; Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)
    Author: Robert Brooks Richardson
    Notes: September 1967
  - Item 6: Reemployment Rights, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)
    Notes: December 1966
- Box: 71, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Defense Manpower and Contract Termination, Publication (Box 71, Folder 39)
    Author: Trevor Bain
- Box: 71, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Improving Productivity in Solid Waste Collection, Publication (Box 71, Folder 40)
    Author: The National Commission on Productivity
- Box: 71, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: More Power to the Regions, Publication (Box 71, Folder 41)
    Author: David Steele
- Box: 71, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Methods and Standards for Guidance, Training and Placement, Publication (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Rehabilitation of Federal Prisoners, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 42)
    Author: U.S. Committee on the Judiciary
    Notes: May 20, 1965
  - Item 3: Rehabilitation in Prepaid Health Care Plans, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 42)
    Author: National Institutes on Rehabilitation
  - Item 4: Professional Examination Service for Vocational Rehabilitation Agencies, Publication (Box 71, Folder 42)
- Box: 71, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: The Effectiveness of Reinstatement as a Public Policy Remedy, Publication (Box 71, Folder 43)
    Author: John E. Drotning & David B. Lipsky
- Box: 71, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Rent Act, Publication (Box 71, Folder 44)
    Author: Tom Vernon
- Box: 71, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Economic Fragments, 1934; Publication (Box 71, Folder 45)
    Author: James Bann
    Notes: March 1934
- Box: 71, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Research Paper Handbook, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 46)
    Author: Robert R. Ruffing
- Box: 71, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Knowledge is Power, 1962; Publication (Box 71, Folder 47)
    Author: New York State University
  - Item 2: Guide to Research Library Resources on Asia, Africa, Russia and East Europe, and Latin America in New York State, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - Item 3: Improving Reference and Research Library Resources in New York State, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 47)
    Notes: June 1965
  - Item 4: Reference and Research Library Resources, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 47)
    Author: James E. Allen
  - Item 5: Knowledge is Power, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 47)
- Box: 71, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: A Paradox of Research Administration, Publication (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Item 2: Scientific Activities of Independent Nonprofit Institutions, 1970; Publication (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Item 3: Research and Studies, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Item 4: The Administration of Government Supported Research at Universities, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 48)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of the Budget
  - Item 5: Federal Research & Demonstration Programs, Publication (Box 71, Folder 48)
- Box: 71, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 71, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Foreign Affairs Research, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 49)
    Author: U.S. Department of State
  - Item 2: Public Versus Private Support of Science, Publication (Box 71, Folder 49)
    Author: Gerald Gordon, Ann Parelius, and Sue Marquis
  - Item 3: Guidelines for Research Grants Under the Manpower Development and Training Act, 1970; Publication (Box 71, Folder 49)
    Notes: December 31, 1970
- Box: 71, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Dead Horse and the Featherbird, 1962; Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: Paul Jacobs
  - Item 2: Special Committee to Study Railroad Problems, 1960; Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: National Association of Railroads
  - Item 3: Railroad Featherbedding Dispute, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Notes: August 29, 1962
  - Item 4: The Menace of Restrictive Work Practices, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Item 5: Unions and the Problems of Retirement, 1959; Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: University of Chicago
    Notes: April 3-4, 1959
  - Item 6: The Work-Rules Dispute, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Item 7: Waste Not Profit Not, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: Robert E. Doherty
  - Item 8: Facts About Featherbedding, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Item 9: Report, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: Royal Commission on Employment of Firemen
  - Item 10: What the Supervisor Should Know and Do, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: Waldo E. Fisher
  - Item 11: Dead Horse and the Featherbird, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Item 12: Revising a Merit-Rating Scheme, Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: A.G.P. Elliot
  - Item 13: The Joint Employee Rating Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Author: Rutgers University
  - Item 14: Changing the Work Rules, 1960; Publication (Box 71, Folder 50)
    Notes: May 1960
- Box: 72, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Changes in Store and Employee Hours, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Author: National Retail Dry Goods Association
  - Item 2: Sales Volume and Employment in British and American Retail Trade, 1962; Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Author: William H. Starbuck
    Notes: December 1962
  - Item 3: Index of Super Market Articles, 1964; Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Author: Super Market Institute
- Box: 72, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A New Look at Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: Geneva Matiasen
  - Item 2: Proceedings, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: National Council on the Aging
    Notes: October 17, 1960
  - Item 3: Company-Initiated Early Retirement as a Means of Work-Force Control, 1963; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: Theron J. Fields
  - Item 4: Flexible Vs. Compulsory Retirement Policies, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: Fred Slavick, John W. McConnell
  - Item 5: A Preview of Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Cooperation Between Industry and Labor in Retirement Education, 1965; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: Woodrow W. Hunter
  - Item 7: Retirement, 1971; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: White House Conference on Aging
  - Item 8: Leadership Training for Pre-Retirement Education, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Preparation for Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: Niagara Falls Division of Adult Education
  - Item 10: Encouraging Effective Preparation for Retirement, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: Ebasco Services Incorporated
    Notes: January 1953
  - Item 11: Current Developments in Preparation for Retirement, 1958; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: National Committee on Aging
    Notes: May 1958
  - Item 12: Preparing Older Workers for Retirement, 1956; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Notes: February 1956
  - Item 13: Civil Servants in Retirement, 1952; Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: R.W. Fleming & Rita McGaughey
  - Item 14: Meeting the Problems of Utilizing Older Workers and Preparing them for Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: L.S. Barrus
  - Item 15: Good Planning to Early Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: New York Civil Service Commission
  - Item 16: Enjoying Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Author: Patricia Shaw
- Box: 72, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Preretirement Education, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Author: University of Michigan
  - Item 2: Retirement Planning, 1960; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Pre-Retirement Education, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Now that You are Retiring, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Planning for the Later Years, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Retirees and Regional Economic Development, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Author: University of Arkansas
  - Item 7: Retirement and Migration in the North Central States, 1968; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Retirement and Migration in the North Central States, 1968; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Retirement and Migration in the North Central States, 1969; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Notes: July 1969
  - Item 10: Retirement and Migration in the North Central States, 1970; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Notes: March 1970
  - Item 11: Retirement and Migration in the North Central States, 1970; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Retirement and Migration in the North Central States, 1970; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Retirement Policies in 194 Companies, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Once in a Lifetime, 1968; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Author: National Association of Retired Civil Employees
    Notes: November 1968
  - Item 15: Financial Problems, 1962; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Author: Retirement Advisors, Inc
  - Item 16: You, the Law, and Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: The Federal Role in Encouraging Preretirement Counseling and New Work Lifetime Patterns, 1969; Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Author: U.S. Special Committee on Aging
    Notes: July 25, 1969
- Box: 72, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Pension Question as Employees See it, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Notes: January 1950
  - Item 2: Successful Pension Planning, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Author: Detroit Trust Company
  - Item 3: Private Pensions and Aged Needs, 1961; Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Author: Martin E. Segal
- Box: 72, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement System, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Author: State of Hawaii
  - Item 2: Das Vermogen der Rentenversicherung in der Diskussion, 1968; Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Author: Des Deutschen Industrieinstituts
  - Item 3: Retirement Plans in Indiana, 1948; Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Author: Indiana Chamber of Commerce
    Notes: June 1948
- Box: 72, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Value of Australian Retirement Plans, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Box: 72, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Pension Plans and Public Policy in California, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Author: State of California
  - Item 2: Pension Plans Under Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Author: California Department of Industrial Relations
- Box: 72, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Pension Plans in California Collective Bargaining Agreemens, 1961; Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Pension Plans Under Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Selected Pension Plans Under Collective Bargaining, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Box: 72, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining and Pensions Conference, 1950; Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
    Author: Ohio Chamber of Commerce
    Notes: March 29, 1950
  - Item 2: Preparation for Retirement, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Where Shall I Live After I Retire, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: What Can I Do to Have a Good Family Life After I Retire, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: How Can I Earn Some Money After I Retire, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: What Can I Do With My Time After I Retire, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: How Can I Keep Healthy in My Later Years, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Your Retirement Years, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: What is Retirement Going to be Like, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Box: 72, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Tax Aspects of Distributions of Pension and Profit Sharing Plans, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Author: Marcus D. Grayck
  - Item 2: The Combination Pension Plan, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Author: Louis K. Neff
  - Item 3: Lump-Sum Distributions Under Qualified Corporate Retirement Plans, 1963; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 22, 1963
  - Item 4: Corporate Pension Funds, 1963; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Notes: May 25, 1963
  - Item 5: Private Noninsured Pension Funds, 1964; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Notes: June 4, 1964
- Box: 72, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Contribution of Pension Funds to the Capital Markets of the EEC, 1968; Publication (Box 72, Folder 11)
    Author: Commission of the European Communities
- Box: 72, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Preservation of Pension Rights, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Pensions in a Free Society, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
    Author: Arthur Seldon
  - Item 3: Company Pension Schemes, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
    Author: Labour Research Department
  - Item 4: Fringe Benefits for Pensioners, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Box: 72, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Debate on Private Pensions, Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
    Author: American Enterprise Institute
- Box: 72, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Superannuation Act, 1967; Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
    Author: The Commonwealth of Australia
  - Item 2: Miglioramenti ai Trattamenti di Quiescenza Delle Casse Pensioni Dei Dipendenti Degli Enti Locali, 1968; Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
    Author: Collana Legislativa e Amministrativa
    Notes: February 5, 1968
    Language: Italian.
- Box: 72, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Canada Pension Plan Act, 1965; Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
    Author: CCH Canadian Limited
- Box: 72, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Handbook, Publication (Box 72, Folder 16)
    Author: State of Minnesota
- Box: 72, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: State Employees' Retirement System of New Jersey, 1947; Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
    Author: State Employees' Retirement System of New Jersey
    Notes: December 31, 1947
- Box: 72, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Industrial Pension and Insurance Plans for Ohio Senior Citizens, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
    Author: Governor's Commision on Aging
  - Item 2: The Major State Retirement Systems, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
    Author: Ohio Legislative Service Commission
- Box: 72, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Retirement and Pension Systems, 1951; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Joseph Schechter
    Notes: October 15, 1951
  - Item 2: Reports, 1954; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Wisconsin Legislature
    Notes: March 1954
  - Item 3: Age and Other Requirements for Retirement on Pension, 1953; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc.
    Notes: May 15, 1953
  - Item 4: Retirement Practices for Older Workers, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: New York Community Council
  - Item 5: Pension and Profit-Sharing Plans, 1967; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Chemical Bank New York Trust Company
    Notes: Autumn 1967
  - Item 6: Private Pension Plans, 1956; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: NPA Business Committee on National Policy
    Notes: December 1956
  - Item 7: Pensions Under Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: William Goldner
  - Item 8: Successful Pension Planning, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Chemical Corn Exchange Bank
  - Item 9: Social Security and Private Pensions at the Crossroads, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Pennsylvania Municipal Retirement and Pension Laws, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Pennsylvania Department of Internal Affairs
  - Item 11: The Stake of Today's Workers in Retirement Security, 1970; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Notes: April 1970
  - Item 12: Pension Aspects of the Economics of Aging, 1970; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Notes: January 1970
  - Item 13: Tax Benefits from Retirement Plans for the Self-Employed, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Robert G. Reynolds
  - Item 14: The Basics of Insured Pension and Profit-Sharing Plans, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: Welfare and Pension Plan Statistics, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 16: Private and Public Pension Plans in the United States, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Institute of Life Insurance
  - Item 17: Public Policy for Private Pensions, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Hewitt Associates
  - Item 18: Chamber of Commerce Retirement Plans, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 19: Extending Private Pension Coverage, 1965; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 20: Association Retirement Plans, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 21: Old-Age Pension Plans and Organizations, 1937; Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Notes: January 5, 1937
  - Item 22: Private Pension Plans and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Financial Executives Institute
  - Item 23: The Five Year Federal Buildup of Pension Issues, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
    Author: Andrew A. Melgard
  - Item 24: Private and Public Pension Plans in the United States, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Box: 72, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Occupational Pension Schemes, Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
    Author: Great Britain Parliament
  - Item 2: A Survey of State and Local Government Retirement Systems, Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: State & Local Government Employment Statistics, 1970; Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Finances of Employee-Retirement Systems, 1964; Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Box: 72, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Public Employee Pension Problem, 1962; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
    Author: Washington Legislative Council
- Box: 72, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Conference on Training and Retraining, Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
    Author: The Brookings Institution
  - Item 2: Retraining the Disadvantaged Worker, Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
    Author: Glen Cain & Gerald Somers
  - Item 3: Active Manpower Policies in Great Britain and Scandinavia, 1966; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Box: 72, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Retraining the Unemployed, 1963; Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
    Notes: November 1963
  - Item 2: Unemployment and Retraining, Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Box: 73, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Retraining in California, 1964; Publication (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Author: California Department of Employment
- Box: 73, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Mesures de Readaptation Appliques en Republique Federale D'Allemagne en Belgique et in France, Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Author: Communaute Europeenne du Charbon et de L'Acier Haute Autorite
- Box: 73, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Our Experience with Retraining and Relocation, Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Author: Gerald G. Somers
- Box: 73, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Active Manpower Policies in Great Britain and Scandinavia, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Box: 73, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Expanding Employability in Ontario, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Author: G.R. Forsyth, J.R. Nininger
- Box: 73, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania Meets the Challenge of Retraining, Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
    Author: Pennsylvania State University
- Box: 73, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Retraining Under the Manpower Development Act, 1964; Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Author: David A. Page
- Box: 73, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Factors in Workers' Decisions to Forego Retraining Under the Manpower Development and Training Act, Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Box: 73, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Digest of Laws Pertaining to Industry in Rhode Island, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    Author: Rhode Island Industrial Commission
- Box: 73, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: General Rules and Regulations, 1943; Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
    Author: Rhode Island Department of Labor
- Box: 73, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Why Distinguished Educators Favor Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: 20 Questions About the Right to Work, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: The Why of a Right-to-Work Law, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: The Right of the Right to Work, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Trade Unions Hamstrung, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Author: O.H. Parsons
  - Item 6: Why Distinguished Educators Favor Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Why Journalists Favor Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: 14(b)? The Key Issue, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Author: The Free Society
  - Item 9: 14(b)? The Key Issue, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 1966, Copy 2
  - Item 10: The Right of the Right to Work, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Notes: Copy 2
  - Item 11: The Legal and Moral Basis of Right to Work Laws, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Author: J.C. Gibson
  - Item 12: The Case for Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Why Employers Should Work for the Right to Work, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: The Right to Work Question, 1968; Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: The Public Looks at 14(b) and the Right to Work Issue, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Box: 73, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Right to Work Laws and the Common Good, Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Author: Jerome L. Toner
  - Item 2: "Right to Work" Laws, Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Author: Bayard Rustin
  - Item 3: Repeal of Section 14(b) of the National Labor Relations Act, 1965; Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Notes: September 9, 1965
  - Item 4: "Right to Work" Laws: Some Economic and Ethical Aspects, 1961; Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Author: William James Lee
  - Item 5: The Right-to-Work Law of Virginia, Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
    Author: Virginia Department of Labor and Industry
  - Item 6: The Right to Work and How to Implement it, 1941; Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)